[BLANK_AUDIO]
These one leg duck squats will [BLEEP] your ass up in the best possible way.
Seriously, they have become one of my favorite lower body exercises.
First of all, they're one of the best glute builders I have done.
Every client of mine that has done these has texted me the following day asking
why their ass was so sore, and they light up your quads too.
They're also incredibly joint friendly.
The duck stance enables you to squat very deep while maintaining an upright torso.
So it's much more low back friendly compared to most squat variations.
Another huge advantage is the loadability.
Instead of being limited to one dumbbell like a goblet squat, you're holding two.
So we have more strength and muscle building potential.
And because you're training one leg at a time, they help improve left to right imbalances.
Two quick coaching cues.
Make sure you turn the back foot out like a duck and stay up on your toes.
And notice my grip.
The dumbbell of the front leg stays at my side while the other one is held in front of my body.
I call it the L grip.
It feels way more natural and prevents the dumbbells from hitting your legs.
FYI, these are one of the signature exercises in my new Lean Bastard program,
which drops in August.
But if you want early access, comment Lean and I'll send you the link to join the VIP list.
These one leg duck squats will f***.